

# JEREMY DAVID

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am solution oriented and flexible developer who thrives in challenging problems and enjoys working on projects.

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Html, Css, Bootstrap, Scss, Tailwindcss, Javascript, Jquery, Reactjs, Gatsbyjs, Nodejs, Mongodb, Git, Php, Wordpress, Shopify, Graphql

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER itreat 2020 - Present

# WEB DEVELOPER Fullstack HQ 2018-2019

- Convert PSD to Pixel Perfect HTML
- Convert PSD to Custom theme Wordpress
- Develop React Sites
- Develop or modify Shopify themes
- Integration

# WEB DEVELOPER INTERN Sparkfn 2017-2018

- Help Senior Devs in their task
- Email Templates

#### **GET IN CONTACT**

+971551840875 jeremydb.david@gmail.com https://jeremydavid.netlify.app/ Dubai, UAE

### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

HOLY ANGEL UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, 2018

- Member of League of Outstanding Programmers
- Member of Code Geeks

MACCIM ROYAL ACADEMY High School, 2014